Leave us alone.
So I didn't post that last post as an I told you so.
I posted it to once again demonstrate that I am a resource for guidance in that I have pattern recognition and I can often see things.
And when we are able to see things before they come, we can prepare.
And I interviewed some members of Korean organization, Naruto, yesterday, and they said that one thing about Korea is that everyone knows who the real enemy is.
And the thing that frustrates me more than anything here in the United States is that we are constantly arguing about who the real enemy is.
And so many of you all participate in making people like me, the truth tellers, the seers, the enemy.
When we are trying so hard to be a resource, knowing how dangerous that is, knowing that makes us a target.
Knowing that that is not what they want.
What's happening in D.C. will happen on a higher level.
It will happen across the nation.
And right now they may be doing checkpoints about immigration, but those checkpoints are going to expand.
Expand criminality will expand in terms of what they determine to be criminality.
And I am not being hyperbolic when I say that if we don't collectively stop arguing against people who have committed themselves to doing the work, the research, the understanding.
That some of us aren't even capable of, not because they don't have the skills, but because we don't have the time, then we are enabling the enemy.